

ROMAN BELOVOLOV

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced software developer with the emphasis on web applications. I possess deep understanding of programing concepts and algorithms, as well as fundamental aspects of Internet and network protocols.

As a worker I established myself as responsible, reliable, deep-thinking and constantly self-developing (see references)

CONTACT

Location: Auckland City, New Zealand

Phone: 020 4471047

Email: belovolovri@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/roman-

belovolov/

REFERENCES

ALEXANDER MARKOV

Head of department, CentrBank of Russia

Phone: +7 916 643 60 97 **Email:** MarkovAV@cbr.ru

PAUL PANG

Professor, research supervisor, Unitec
WeChat ID: paulspang
Email: ppang@unitec.ac.nz

JEFF YUAN

Senior Software Developer, Unitec Phone: +64 210 885 3368 Email: jyuan@unitec.ac.nz

SKILLS

Technologies React HTML CSS3 Gulp NPM Git Webpack D3.js

Javascript Python C# PHP

Node.js Express.js ASP.NET Core Flask

MongoDB SQL Linux Windows

AWS Google Cloud Heroku

Industry knowledge Software development Cyber-security Payment sys-

tems Machine Learning IoT Networks Web Development (MVC, SPA, RESTful API)

EXPERIENCE

Web developer UNITEC INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

AUCKLAND

Sep 2017 - present (11 months)

Fullstack web-developent on Javascript with React and Node.js. Initially developed a JSON/CSV API for the Unitec's Auckland air quality project. Currently working on food & environment

traceability research project.

Leading techical CENTRAL engineer MOSCOW

CENTRAL BANK OF RUSSIA

Nov 2013 - Jun 2017 (3 years 8 months) Work primarily included:

- technical support (tiers 2-3) of a multi-component payment system along with additional automated systems;

deployment of testing environments, stress tests;

- automation of work tasks by scripting and programming;

System integrator & administrator

FORMULASTROYPROYEKT

MOSCOW

Nov 2013 - Jun 2017 (3 years 8 months) Developed, set up and documented the IT-infrastructure of an office with 30 employees, then delegated the administration. Infrastructure included Active Directory, SMB file share, IP-PBX(Asterisk), dual-WAN in active-passive mode, Wi-Fi, cli-

ent-server antivirus, VPN

EDUCATION

2017 - 2018 Graduate Dipoma in Computing

UNITEC INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

AUCKLAND

Majoring in Software Development I took courses in Web Development, Databases, Machine Learning, IoT, GUI pro-

gramming

2009 - 2014 Specialist Diploma in Information security

NATIONAL RESEARCH NUCLEAR UNIVERSITY "MEPhI"

MOSCOW

Among subjects were: Network security, Application security, Cryptography, Programming, Algorithms

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Learned a lot of practical programming on FreeCodeCamp and Udemy courses, such as "ES6 Javascript: The Complete Developer's Guide", "The Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp", "Node with React: Fullstack Web Development", "Git a Web Developer Job: Mastering the Modern Workflow" and others.